April poetry challenge day 11 number 11
everyone loves this out beyond ideas of
wrongdoing and right doing there is a
field I'll meet you there but I've
noticed what the faces of people hearing
this poem for the first time or the
umpteenth time look like where they go
what they are feeling their faces
outlining the story in their heads
giving away the feeling tone of their
hearts I witnessed them walking into
fields of Alpine blossoms silver waters
running through rainbows lovers feeding
each other's grapes at their picnic
place dear sleeping with their fawns
nearby winds gentle and warm the sky a
tremendous blue smelling a baby's
breaths and puppies but that's not what
he said the invitation is not to a field
of for example grass is rising with
poppies in bliss charged as they are
with ideas of right born of a stunted
imagination the invitation is not to a
field of cattle and Greek yeast
returning to nature where we are all
equally and happily because that's not
what he said can you put there instead
on the canvas of your imagination only
shapes feeling colors and tones that do
not fit the categories of ideas right or
wrong good or evil saved or damned
that's what he is saying and when you do
if you can you will realize something
that will drop that expression off your
face and replace it with horror knowing
we are already there we are already that